Correspondence from the Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge Foundation Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence, 1894-1953 (Box 1-109)
  - Hess, Lara Straus (Mrs. Alfred F. Hess) (Box-folder 40/42)
  - Hess, Myra (Box-folder 40/43)
  - Hewitt, Maurice (Box-folder 40/44)
  - Heyner, Herbert (Box-folder 40/45)
  - "Hi" miscellaneous see also "H" miscellaneous (Box-folder 40/46)
  - Hibbard, Charles L. and Alice (Box-folder 40/47)
  - Hier, Ethel Glenn (Box-folder 40/48)
  - Hijman, Julius (Box-folder 40/49)
  - "Hil" miscellaneous see also "H" miscellaneous (Box-folder 41/1)
  - Hilb, Emil (Box-folder 41/2)
  - Hill, Arthur F. (Box-folder 41/3)
  - Hill, Christabel (Box-folder 41/4)
  - Hill, David J. (Box-folder 41/5)
  - Hill, Edward Burlingame, 1919-1929 (Box-folder 41/6)
  - Hill, Edward Burlingame, 1930-1933 (Box-folder 41/7)
  - Hill, Edward Burlingame, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 41/8)
  - Hill, Edward Burlingame, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 41/9)
  - Hill, Edward Burlingame, undated (Box-folder 41/10)
  - Hill, Mabel Wood see Wood Hill, Mabel
  - Hill School (Pottstown, Pa.) (Box-folder 41/11)
  - Hillard, Mary R. (Box-folder 41/12)
  - Hillyer, H. Stanley see Washington Square (N.Y.) Association
  - Hillyer, Raphael (Box-folder 41/13)
  - "Hin" miscellaneous see also "H" miscellaneous (Box-folder 41/14)
  - Hindemith, Paul and Gertrude (Box-folder 41/15)
  - Hinman, Mildred (Box-folder 41/16)
  - Hinners, Howard see Wellesley College. Hinners, Howard
  - Hinton, Arthur and Katharine Gordon (Box-folder 41/17)
  - Hirsch, Olga (Box-folder 41/18)
  - Hitchcock, Myrtle see Los Angeles. Hotels. Hitchcock, Myrtle
  - "Ho" miscellaneous see also "H" miscellaneous (Box-folder 41/19)
  - Hobbs, Jane W. (Box-folder 41/20)
  - Hobden, Ethel (Box-folder 41/21)
  - Hobdoes, Ethel see Hobden, Ethel
  - Hobron, Marie L. (Box-folder 41/22)
  - Hoérée, Arthur (Box-folder 41/23)
  - Hoeven, C. van der see van der Hoeven, C.
  - Hoffman, Gertrude (Mrs. Ralph Hoffmann), undated (presumed early) (Box-folder 41/24)
  - Hoffman, Gertrude, 1926-1929 (Box-folder 41/25)
  - Hoffman, Gertrude, 1930-1939 (Box-folder 41/26)
  - Hoffman, Gertrude, 1940-1953 (Box-folder 41/27)
  - Hoffman, Gertrude, undated (presumed late) (Box-folder 41/28)
  - Hoffmann, Richard (Box-folder 41/29)
  - Hoffmann, Rolf (Box-folder 41/30)
  - Hofmann, Heinrich (Box-folder 41/31)
  - Hofmann, Josef (Box-folder 41/32)
  - Holden, Frances Colman (Box-folder 41/33)
  - Hollman, Joseph (Box-folder 41/34)
  - Holloway, Mary V. (Box-folder 41/35)
  - Hollywood Bowl (Los Angeles, Calif.) (Box-folder 41/36)
  - Holmes, Malcolm (Box-folder 41/37)
  - Holmes, Rebecca W. (Box-folder 41/38)
  - Holsinger, Walter Denman (Box-folder 41/39)
  - Holst, Gustav (Box-folder 41/40)
  - Homberg, Jeanne (Box-folder 41/41)
  - Homer, Louise and Sidney (Box-folder 41/42)
  - "Hon" miscellaneous see also "H" miscellaneous (Box-folder 42/1)
  - Honegger, Arthur (Box-folder 42/2)
  - Honegger, Henri (Box-folder 42/3)
  - Honolulu Academy of Arts, Includes one item from Honolulu Symphony Society. (Box-folder 42/4)
  - Honolulu Art Society (Box-folder 42/5)
  - Hoogstraten, Willem van (Box-folder 42/6)
  - Hooker, Adelaide (Box-folder 42/7)
  - Hoover, Lou Henry (Mrs. Herbert) see Stanford University. Hoover, Lou Henry
  - Hope, May MacDonald (Box-folder 42/8)
  - Hopekirk, Helen (Box-folder 42/9)
  - Horne, Margaret (Box-folder 42/10)
  - Horowitz, Vladimir (Box-folder 42/12)
  - Horszowski, Mieczyslaw (letter to only) (Box-folder 42/11)
  - Housman, Rosalie (Box-folder 42/13)
  - Hovhaness, Alan (Box-folder 42/14)
  - Howard, Shafter (Box-folder 42/15)
  - Howard University (Box-folder 42/16)
  - Howe, Mark A. DeWolfe (Box-folder 42/17)
  - Howe, Mary, 1923-1929 (Box-folder 42/18)
  - Howe, Mary, 1930-1935 (Box-folder 42/19)
  - Howe, Mary, 1936-1939 (Box-folder 42/20)
  - Howe, Mary, 1940-1953 (Box-folder 42/21)
  - Howe, Mary, undated (Box-folder 42/22)
  - Howe, Merwin (Box-folder 42/23)
  - Howes, Arthur see Organ Institute of America
  - Hoyt, Thatcher, Mrs. see Fergus, Phyllis
  - Hozack, W. (Box-folder 42/24)
  - "Hu" miscellaneous see also "H" miscellaneous (Box-folder 42/25)
  - Hubay, Jenõ (Box-folder 42/26)
  - Hubbard, Frank (Box-folder 42/27)
  - Huebsch, B. W. (Box-folder 42/28)
  - Hüttel, Joseph (Box-folder 42/29)
  - Huggler, John (Box-folder 42/30)
  - Hughes, Adella Prentiss (Box-folder 42/31)
  - Hughes, Edwin see National Music Council
  - Hughes, Herbert (Box-folder 42/33)
  - Hughes, Margo (Box-folder 42/34)
  - Hull, Anne (Box-folder 42/35)
  - Hull, Cordell see U.S. Secretary of State
  - Hull House (Chicago, Ill.) (Box-folder 42/36)
  - Human, Alfred see Musical America
  - Hungary (Box-folder 42/37)
  - Hunn, Doris Adams (Box-folder 42/38)
  - Hunt, Horace (Box-folder 42/39)
  - Hunter College (Box-folder 42/40)
  - Huntington (Henry E.) Library and Art Gallery (Box-folder 42/41)
  - Hurok, Sol (Box-folder 42/42)
  - Huse, Harry Pinckney, Mrs. (Box-folder 42/43)
  - Huss, Henry Holden (Box-folder 42/44)
  - "Hut" miscellaneous see also "H" miscellaneous (Box-folder 43/1)
  - Hutcheson, Ernest and Irmgart, 1917-1928 (Box-folder 43/2)
  - Hutcheson, Ernest and Irmgart, 1931-1941 (Box-folder 43/3)
  - Hutcheson, Ernest and Irmgart, undated (Box-folder 43/4)
  - Hutchins, Robert M. see Chicago University. Hutchins, Robert M.
  - Hutchinson, Charles L. (Box-folder 43/5)
  - Hutchinson, Estelle Gould (Box-folder 43/6)
  - Huybrechts, Albert (Box-folder 43/7)
  - "Hy" miscellaneous see also "H" miscellaneous (Box-folder 43/8)
  - Hyde, Florence (Box-folder 43/9)
  - Hyde, Henry St. John (Box-folder 43/10)
  - Hyde, Herbert E. (Box-folder 43/11)
  - "H" not further identified (Box-folder 43/12)
  - "H" "see references" (Box-folder 43/13)
  - "I" miscellaneous (Box-folder 43/14)
  - Iarecki, Tadeusz (Box-folder 43/15)
  - Ibbs and Tillett (Box-folder 43/16)
  - Ibert, Jacques (Box-folder 43/17)
  - Ickes, Harold, Mrs. (letter to) (Box-folder 43/18)
  - Ideler, Edwin and Pearl (Box-folder 43/19)
  - Illiashenko, André S. (Box-folder 43/20)
  - Illingworth, Elsie see National Broadcasting Company. Illingworth, Elsie
  - Illingworth, Nelson (Box-folder 43/21)
  - Ilsley, Samuel M. (Box-folder 43/22)
  - Indiana University see also Rossi, Urico (Box-folder 43/23)
  - Indianapolis Symphony Orchestra (Box-folder 43/24)
  - Inge, C. C. (Box-folder 43/25)
  - Ingelbrecht, D. E. (Box-folder 43/26)
  - Ingerson, Frank (Box-folder 43/27)
  - International Composers' Guild (Box-folder 43/28)
  - International Society for Contemporary Music see also Stefan, Paul (Box-folder 43/29)
  - International Student Center, Cambridge, Mass. (Box-folder 43/30)
  - Ireland, John (Box-folder 43/31)
  - Irion, Yolanda Meró (Box-folder 43/32)
  - Irish, Leiland Atherton, Mrs. (Box-folder 43/33)
  - Irvine, Libby (Box-folder 43/34)
  - Isadora Duncan Society see Duncan, Isadora, Society
  - Isbell, Charles W. (Box-folder 43/35)
  - Isham, Edwin (Box-folder 43/36)
  - Italy (Box-folder 43/37)
  - Ives, Charles Edward and Mrs. (Box-folder 43/38)
  - Ives, Henry G. (Box-folder 43/39)
  - Ivimey, Joseph (Box-folder 43/40)
  - "J" miscellaneous (Box-folder 43/41)
  - Jacobi, Frederick and Irene, undated, Presumed early, before 1935. (Box-folder 43/42)
  - Jacobi, Frederick and Irene, 1922-1928 (Box-folder 43/43)
  - Jacobi, Frederick and Irene, 1930-1936 (Box-folder 43/44)
  - Jacobi, Frederick and Irene, 1937-1939 (Box-folder 43/45)
  - Jacobi, Frederick and Irene, 1940-1953 (Box-folder 43/46)
  - Jacobi, Frederick and Irene, undated (Box-folder 43/47)
  - Jacob's Pillow (Box-folder 43/48)
  - Jacobsen, Sascha (Box-folder 43/49)
  - Jacquemain, A. (Box-folder 43/50)
  - "Jam" miscellaneous see also "J" miscellaneous (Box-folder 44/1)
  - James, Alice see Longy School of Music
  - James, Helen (Box-folder 44/2)
  - James, Ivor (Box-folder 44/3)
  - James, Philip (Box-folder 44/4)
  - James, William and Alice (Box-folder 44/5)
  - Jameson, J. Franklin see Library of Congress. Miscellany
  - Jameson, Mary (Box-folder 44/6)
  - Janssen, Werner (Box-folder 44/7)
  - Jaques-Dalcroze, Émile (Box-folder 44/8)
  - Jarecka, Louise Llewellyn (Box-folder 44/9)
  - Jaubert, Maurice (Box-folder 44/10)
  - Jaulet, Pierre (Box-folder 44/11)
  - "Je" miscellaneous see also "J" miscellaneous (Box-folder 44/12)
  - Jefferson, Mary (Box-folder 44/13)
  - Jennings, Hennen, Mrs. (Box-folder 44/14)
  - Jeremy, Raymond (Box-folder 44/15)
  - Jesinghaus, Walter (Box-folder 44/16)
  - "Jo" miscellaneous see also "J" miscellaneous (Box-folder 44/17)
  - Johansen, Gunnar, 1935-1939 (Box-folder 44/18)
  - Johansen, Gunnar, 1940-1948 (Box-folder 44/19)
  - Johansen, Gunnar, undated (Box-folder 44/20)
  - John Powell Foundation see Powell, John, Foundation
  - John Simon Guggenehim Memorial Foundation see Guggenheim Foundation
  - Johns, Clayton (Box-folder 44/21)
  - Johnson, H. Earle (Box-folder 44/22)
  - Johnson, James P. (Box-folder 44/23)
  - Johnson, Lockrem (Box-folder 44/24)
  - Johnson, Reber (Box-folder 44/25)
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood (Box-folder 44/26)
  - Jokl, Otto (Box-folder 44/27)
  - Jones, Isabel A. (Box-folder 44/28)
  - Jones, Isabel Morse (Box-folder 44/29)
  - Jones, Katharine Lee (Box-folder 44/30)
  - Jones, Mary Elizabeth see Pittsfield, Mass. Community Music School
  - Jongen, Joseph (Box-folder 44/31)
  - Josten, Werner (Box-folder 44/32)
  - "Ju" miscellaneous see also "J" miscellaneous (Box-folder 44/33)
  - Judson, Arthur (concert management), 1922-1929 see also Columbia Concert Management (Box-folder 44/34)
  - Judson, Arthur (concert management), 1930-1936 (Box-folder 44/35)
  - Judson, Arthur (concert management), 1937-1940 (Box-folder 44/36)
  - Juilliard School of Music (Box-folder 44/37)
  - Juilliard String Quartet (Box-folder 44/38)
  - Julber, Ovady (Box-folder 44/39)
  - "K" miscellaneous (Box-folder 44/40)
  - Kahan, Salomón (Box-folder 44/41)
  - Kahgan, Philip (Box-folder 44/42)
  - Kahn, Erich Itor, 1945-1949 (Box-folder 44/43)
  - Kahn, Erich Itor, 1950-1953, undated (Box-folder 44/44)
  - Kahn, Erminie (Box-folder 44/45)
  - Kahn, Mädie Kneisel (Box-folder 44/46)
  - "Kal" miscellaneous see also "K" miscellaneous (Box-folder 45/1)
  - Kalisch, A. (Box-folder 45/2)
  - Kalischer, Clemens (Box-folder 45/3)
  - Kallen, Horace M. see New School for Social Research
  - Kaltenborn, Franz (Box-folder 45/4)
  - Kanitz, Ernst (Box-folder 45/5)
  - Kansas City, Missouri: Chamber Music Society of (Box-folder 45/7)
  - Kansas City, Missouri. University of Kansas City, 1937-1939 (Box-folder 45/8)
  - Kansas City, Missouri. University of Kansas City, 1940-1948 (Box-folder 45/9)
  - Kansas City University see Kansas City, Missouri. University of Kansas City
  - Kansas, University of (Box-folder 45/6)
  - Karrick, David Brewer (Box-folder 45/10)
  - Kastner, Alfred (Box-folder 45/11)
  - Katims, Milton (Box-folder 45/12)
  - Katz, Hanns L. (Box-folder 45/13)
  - Kauffman, Lesser (Box-folder 45/14)
  - Kaufman, Louis (Box-folder 45/15)
  - "Ke" miscellaneous see also "K" miscellaneous (Box-folder 45/16)
  - Keim, A. (Box-folder 45/17)
  - Keller, Harrison (Box-folder 45/18)
  - Keller, Helen (fund appeals only) (Box-folder 45/19)
  - Kelley, Edgar Stillman and Mrs. (Box-folder 45/20)
  - Kelly, Cuthbert (Box-folder 45/21)
  - "Ken" miscellaneous see also "K" miscellaneous (Box-folder 45/22)
  - Kennedy, Charles Rann and Edith Wynne (Box-folder 45/23)
  - Kenton, Egon (Box-folder 45/24)
  - Kenyon College (Box-folder 45/25)
  - Kerby, Marion (Box-folder 45/26)
  - Kerntler, Eugène (Box-folder 45/27)
  - Kerntler, Kálmán (Box-folder 45/28)
  - Key, Pierre V. R. (Box-folder 45/29)
  - Khuner, Felix (Box-folder 45/30)
  - "Ki" miscellaneous see also "K" miscellaneous (Box-folder 45/31)
  - Kieckhoefer, Marie (Box-folder 45/32)
  - Kikutchi (Box-folder 45/33)
  - Kimball, Eva (Box-folder 45/34)
  - Kimberley, Elsie S. (Box-folder 45/35)
  - "Kin" miscellaneous see also "K" miscellaneous (Box-folder 46/1)
  - Kindler, Hans, 1918-1925 (Box-folder 46/2)
  - Kindler, Hans, 1926 (Box-folder 46/3)
  - Kindler, Hans, 1927 (Box-folder 46/4)
  - Kindler, Hans, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 46/5)
  - Kindler, Hans, 1930-1932 (Box-folder 46/6)
  - Kindler, Hans, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 46/7)
  - Kindler, Hans, 1935-1939 (Box-folder 46/8)
  - Kindler, Hans, 1940-1949 (Box-folder 46/9)
  - Kindler, Hans, undated (Box-folder 46/10)
  - King, Louisa (Box-folder 46/11)
  - King, Richard, Dr. (Box-folder 46/12)
  - King and Queen Training School, Newtown, Va. (Box-folder 46/13)
  - King-Coit School and Children's Theatre (Box-folder 46/14)
  - Kingman, Russell B. (Box-folder 46/15)
  - Kinkeldey, Otto see also New York Public Library (Box-folder 46/16)
  - "Kip" miscellaneous see also "K" miscellaneous (Box-folder 46/17)
  - Kirkpatrick, John (Box-folder 46/18)
  - Kirkpatrick, Ralph (Box-folder 46/19)
  - Kirstein, Lincoln (Box-folder 46/20)
  - Kitson, Henry and Marie, 1932-1939 (Box-folder 46/21)
  - Kitson, Henry and Marie, 1940-circa 1950 (Box-folder 46/22)
  - Kitson, Henry and Marie, undated (Box-folder 46/23)
  - "Kl" miscellaneous see also "K" miscellaneous (Box-folder 47/1)
  - Klemperer, Otto (Box-folder 47/2)
  - Kletzki, Paul (Box-folder 47/3)
  - "Kn" miscellaneous see also "K" miscellaneous (Box-folder 47/4)
  - Kneisel, Frank (Box-folder 47/5)
  - Kneisel, Franz and Marianne (Box-folder 47/6)
  - Kneisel, Mädie see Kahn, Mädie Kneisel
  - Knight, Francis M. see Ravinia Festival
  - Knittel, Fritz (Box-folder 47/7)
  - Knopf, Alfred A. (Box-folder 47/8)
  - "Ko" miscellaneous see also "K" miscellaneous (Box-folder 47/9)
  - Kobbé, Gustav (Box-folder 47/10)
  - Kochanska, Sophie (Box-folder 47/11)
  - Kochnitzky, Léon (Box-folder 47/12)
  - Kœchlin, Charles (Box-folder 47/13)
  - Koenen, Tilly (Box-folder 47/14)
  - Kolisch, Rudolf, 1934-1937 (Box-folder 47/15)
  - Kolisch, Rudolf, 1938 (Box-folder 47/16)
  - Kolisch, Rudolf, 1939 (Box-folder 47/17)
  - Kolisch, Rudolf, 1940-1942 (Box-folder 47/18)
  - Kolisch, Rudolf, 1944-1951 (Box-folder 47/19)
  - Kolisch, Rudolf, undated (Box-folder 47/20)
  - Kolodin, Irving (Box-folder 47/21)
  - "Koo" miscellaneous see also "K" miscellaneous (Box-folder 48/1)
  - Koons, Walter see National Broadcasting Company. Koons, Walter
  - Kornauth, Egon (Box-folder 48/2)
  - Korngold, Erich Wolfgang (Box-folder 48/3)
  - Kornsand, Emil (Box-folder 48/4)
  - Kornstein, Egon see Kenton, Egon
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1916-1917 (Box-folder 49/1)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1918-1920 (Box-folder 49/2)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1921-1922 (Box-folder 49/3)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 49/4)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1925-1927 (Box-folder 49/5)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 49/6)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1930 (Box-folder 49/7)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1931 (Box-folder 49/8)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1932 (Box-folder 49/9)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1933 (Box-folder 49/10)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1934 (Box-folder 49/11)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 49/12)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1937 (Box-folder 50/1)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1938 (Box-folder 50/2)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 50/3)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1941-1943 (Box-folder 50/4)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1944-1949 (Box-folder 50/5)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 50/6)
  - Kortschak, Hugo and Alice, undated (Box-folder 50/7)
  - Kosciuszko Foundation (Box-folder 48/5)
  - Koshetz, Nina (Box-folder 48/6)
  - Koshland, Cora Schweitzer (Box-folder 48/7)
  - Koussevitzky, Serge and Olga, 1932-1936 (Box-folder 48/8)
  - Koussevitzky, Serge and Olga, 1940-1953 (Box-folder 48/9)
  - Koussevitzky, Serge and Olga, undated (Box-folder 48/10)
  - Koutzen, Boris (Box-folder 48/11)
  - "Kr" miscellaneous see also "K" miscellaneous (Box-folder 48/12)
  - Kraeuter, Karl H. (Box-folder 48/13)
  - Kraeuter, Phyllis (Box-folder 48/14)
  - Kramer, A. Walter see Musical America: Kramer, A. Walter]
  - Kréal, Ernest (Box-folder 48/15)
  - Krehbiel, Henry Edward (Box-folder 48/16)
  - Kreiner, Edward and Mrs. (Box-folder 48/17)
  - Kreisler, Fritz (Box-folder 48/18)
  - Krenek, Ernst (Box-folder 48/19)
  - Kreshover, Charles (Box-folder 48/20)
  - Kresz, Géza de see also De Kresz, Géza and Hart House String Quartet (Box-folder 48/21)
  - Křička, Jaroslav (Box-folder 48/22)
  - Krips, Alfred and Helen (Box-folder 48/23)
  - Kroll, William and Pearl, 1923-1929 (Box-folder 51/1)
  - Kroll, William and Pearl, 1930-1933 (Box-folder 51/2)
  - Kroll, William and Pearl, 1934 (Box-folder 51/3)
  - Kroll, William and Pearl, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 51/4)
  - Kroll, William and Pearl, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 51/5)
  - Kroll, William and Pearl, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 51/6)
  - Kroll, William and Pearl, 1941-1943 (Box-folder 51/7)
  - Kroll, William and Pearl, 1944-1949 (Box-folder 51/8)
  - Kroll, William and Pearl, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 51/9)
  - Kroll, William and Pearl, undated, From the 160 West 87th Street residence. (Box-folder 51/10)
  - Kroll, William and Pearl, undated, From the 50 West 67th Street residence. (Box-folder 51/11)
  - Kroll, William and Pearl, undated, From the 105 West 73rd Street residence. (Box-folder 51/12)
  - Kroll, William and Pearl, undated, From the 244 Riveside Drive residence. (Box-folder 51/13)
  - Kroll, William and Pearl, undated, From various addresses. (Box-folder 51/14)
  - Krone, Max T. (Box-folder 48/24)
  - Kronke, Emil (Box-folder 48/25)
  - Kroyt, Boris (Box-folder 48/26)
  - "Ku" miscellaneous see also "K" miscellaneous (Box-folder 48/27)
  - Küstermeier, Rudolf (Box-folder 48/28)
  - Kunz, Felix (Box-folder 48/29)
  - Kurenko, Maria (Box-folder 48/30)
  - "L" miscellaneous (Box-folder 48/31)
  - Laberge, Bernard see also Colbert-Laberge Concert Management (Box-folder 48/32)
  - Labunski, Felix (Box-folder 48/33)
  - La Fontaine, Henry (Box-folder 48/34)
  - Laidler, Harry W. see League for Industrial Democracy
  - Lajtha, László (Box-folder 48/35)
  - Lally, Howard (Box-folder 48/36)
  - Lambert, Alexander (Box-folder 48/37)
  - Lambert, Pierre (Box-folder 48/38)
  - Lamond, Felix and Margaret (Box-folder 48/39)
  - "Lan" miscellaneous see also "L" miscellaneous (Box-folder 48/40)
  - Land, Harold (Box-folder 48/41)
  - Landmann, H. C. (Box-folder 48/42)
  - Landowska, Wanda (Box-folder 48/43)
  - Landre, Willem (Box-folder 48/44)
  - Landshoff, Werner see Vielle Trio
  - Lang, Malcolm (Box-folder 48/45)
  - Lang, Margaret Ruthven (Box-folder 48/46)
  - Lange, Hans (Box-folder 48/47)
  - Langendoen, J. C. (Box-folder 48/48)
  - Langenus, Gustave (Box-folder 48/49)
  - Langley, Allan Lincoln (Box-folder 48/50)
  - Langley, Beatrice J. (Box-folder 48/51)
  - Lanier, Harriet (Box-folder 48/52)
  - Lansburgh, Julius, Mrs. (Box-folder 48/53)
  - Lansing, Robert and Eleanor (Box-folder 48/54)
  - Lanzer, Carl (Box-folder 48/55)
  - "Lap" miscellaneous see also "L" miscellaneous (Box-folder 52/1)
  - Lapham, Evadna (Box-folder 52/2)
  - Lapidus, George (Box-folder 52/3)
  - Laporte, Lucien (Box-folder 52/4)
  - La Prade, Ernest see National Broadcasting Company. La Prade, Ernest
  - LaRue, Jan see Wellesley College. LaRue, Jan
  - Laskine, Lily (Box-folder 52/5)
  - Lattuada, Felice (Box-folder 52/6)
  - "Lau" miscellaneous see also "L" miscellaneous (Box-folder 52/7)
  - Laurent, Georges (Box-folder 52/8)
  - Laurinburg Normal and Industrial Institute (Box-folder 52/9)
  - Lausanne. Université (Box-folder 52/10)
  - LaViolette, Wesley (Box-folder 52/11)
  - Lawrence, Lucile (Box-folder 52/12)
  - Lawton, Dorothy (Box-folder 52/13)
  - Lawton, Mary (Box-folder 52/14)
  - Lazan, Albert and Helen (Box-folder 52/15)
  - "Le" miscellaneous see also "L" miscellaneous (Box-folder 52/16)
  - League for Industrial Democracy (Box-folder 52/17)
  - League of Composers. Reis, Claire R., 1922-1934 (Box-folder 52/18)
  - League of Composers. Reis, Claire R., 1937-1947 (Box-folder 52/19)
  - League of Composers: miscellany (Box-folder 52/20)
  - Le Bœuf, Henry (Box-folder 52/21)
  - Ledent, René (Box-folder 52/22)
  - Lederman, Minna (Box-folder 52/23)
  - Lee, Dai-Keong (letter to) (Box-folder 52/24)
  - Lee, Dorothy see Stanford University. Friends of Music
  - Lee, Julia Tolman (Box-folder 52/25)
  - Leedy, Charles Denoe see Mount Holyoke College. Leedy, Charles Denoe
  - Legge, Robin H. (Box-folder 52/26)
  - Leginska, Ethel (Box-folder 52/27)
  - Legion of Honor see France. Legion of Honor
  - Leichtentritt, Hugo (Box-folder 52/28)
  - Leiser, Clara M. (Box-folder 52/29)
  - Le Maire, Josef (Box-folder 52/30)
  - Lenox Quartet (Box-folder 52/31)
  - Lenox, Mass. (Box-folder 52/32)
  - Lenski, Vladimir (Box-folder 52/33)
  - Lent, Sylvia see Frankenstein, Alfred and Sylvia
  - Leon, [illegible] (Box-folder 52/34)
  - "Ler" miscellaneous see also "L" miscellaneous (Box-folder 52/35)
  - Le Roy, René, 1930-1935 (Box-folder 52/36)
  - Le Roy, René, 1936-1943, undated (Box-folder 52/37)
  - Leschetizky, Marie Gabrielle (Box-folder 52/38)
  - Lester, Margaret and William (Box-folder 52/39)
  - Letz, Hans (Box-folder 52/40)
  - Levant, Oscar (Box-folder 52/41)
  - Levarie, Siegmund (Box-folder 52/42)
  - Levey, James (Box-folder 52/43)
  - Levine, Marks see National Broadcasting Company: Levine, Marks
  - Levitzki, Mischa (Box-folder 52/44)
  - Levy, John (Box-folder 52/45)
  - Lewis, Alfred Baker see Socialist Party of the United States of America
  - Lewis, Marx see Socialist Party of the United States of America
  - Lewisohn, Irene (Box-folder 52/46)
  - Lewyn, Helena (Box-folder 52/47)
  - Lhévinne, Josef (Box-folder 52/48)
  - Lhoest, Liliane (Box-folder 52/49)
  - "Li" miscellaneous see also "L" miscellaneous (Box-folder 52/50)
  - Library of Congress. Clapp, Verner W. (Box-folder 53/1)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, undated, These are probably pre-1933. (Box-folder 54/1)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1922-1923 (Box-folder 54/2)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1924 (Box-folder 54/3)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1925 (Box-folder 54/4)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1926 (Box-folder 54/5)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1927 (Box-folder 54/6)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1928 (Box-folder 54/7)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1929 (Box-folder 54/8)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1930 (Box-folder 54/9)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1931 (Box-folder 55/1)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1932 (Box-folder 55/2)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1933 (Box-folder 55/3)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1933 (carbons) (Box-folder 55/4)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1934 (Box-folder 55/5)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1935 (Box-folder 55/6)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1936 (Box-folder 55/7)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1937, Jan.-Oct. (Box-folder 55/8)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1937, Nov.-Dec. (Box-folder 55/9)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1938 (Box-folder 55/10)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1939-1944, 1983 (Box-folder 55/11)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, 1939-1941 (Box-folder 55/12)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, undated, These are probably post-1932. (Box-folder 55/13)
  - Library of Congress. Engel, Carl, undated and miscellany (Box-folder 55/14)
  - Library of Congress. Evans, Luther H. (Box-folder 53/2)
  - Library of Congress. Friends of Music in the Library of Congress (Box-folder 53/3)
  - Library of Congress. Legal advice to E.S. Coolidge regarding establishment of Berkshire Music Colony and the Library of Congress foundation (Box-folder 53/4)
  - Library of Congress. MacLeish, Archibald (Box-folder 53/5)
  - Library of Congress. Putnam, Herbert, 1923 (Box-folder 53/6)